<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Connell McCarthy</title>
    <link>https://www.connellmccarthy.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Connell McCarthy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Oct 2020 21:02:12 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://www.connellmccarthy.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Shopify Inbox</title>
      <link>https://www.connellmccarthy.com/article/inbox/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2021 17:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.connellmccarthy.com/article/inbox/</guid>
      <description>How I used my passion projects to create powerful creative for Shopify Inbox. I can’t sit still. Whether it’s taking photos, making music, or building something - my happiness is directly linked to my productivity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One Bill</title>
      <link>https://www.connellmccarthy.com/article/one-bill/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Jan 2021 17:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.connellmccarthy.com/article/one-bill/</guid>
      <description>Building an expense sharing app over the holidays, as a non-developer. If you know me at all, you’ll know that I always have to be doing something. I’m constantly looking for new challenges and skills that I can add to my toolbelt.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Home Office</title>
      <link>https://www.connellmccarthy.com/article/my-home-office/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Oct 2020 17:53:30 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.connellmccarthy.com/article/my-home-office/</guid>
      <description>Designing a productive space that’s conducive to creativity for both work, and personal projects. When looking for our home I was very adamant about finding a place that served my needs for my work from home day-job, but also my after-hours creative projects like music, design, photography, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making A Home</title>
      <link>https://www.connellmccarthy.com/article/making-a-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Oct 2020 11:37:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.connellmccarthy.com/article/making-a-home/</guid>
      <description>In the middle of a worldwide pandemic, we decided it was a good idea to buy a house. We had been looking at houses for a little while before the pandemic, but it was more like window shopping to give us something to do in our free time instead of scrolling endlessly through Instagram.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
